Guide to the Herbert F. Janick Jr. Papers MS 012
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Herbert F. Janick Jr. Papers
1889-2002
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Janick, Herbert F.
MS 012
121
16 Linear Feet, 14 boxes, and 1 OS Folder
The Herbert F. Janick, Jr. Papers spans the years 1889-2002 and consists mainly of Janick's research for his book on the centennial history of Western Connecticut State University.
Provenance
Donated by Herb Janick.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
For 29 years, Dr. Janick taught at WestConn. He retired in 1998 but continues to teach courses at WestConn in urban history and American architecture. Dr. Janick has been instrumental in the research for and the writing of WestConn's centennial history, A People's University: The Centennial History of Western Connecticut State University.
Scope and Content Note
The Herbert F. Janick, Jr. Papers (HFJ) comprise approximately 7 linear feet arranged into three series: 1. Centennial Manuscript; 2. The Center for Urban Studies; and, 3. Subject Files. The collection spans the years 1889-2002 and consists mainly of HFJ's research for his book on the centennial history of Western Connecticut State University.
Series 1 consists of correspondence, student publications, theses, local newspaper articles, instructional programs, course catalogs, scrapbooks, and interviews with present and former faculty, administrators, students and friends.
Additional information regarding accreditation, admissions, educational programs, Faculty Senate, student activities and publications, and university publications can be found in the University Archives and in the following Manuscript Collections: Truman Warner Collection, Geddes Collection, Jack V. Friel University History Collection, James Furman Collection, June Goodman Collection, Ruth A. Haas Papers, and Ralph C. Jenkins Papers.
The scrapbook files in this collection are composed of local newspaper articles and summaries of articles that chronicle the growth of Danbury Normal School to a state university.
The Histories files include Charlotte Isham's History of Western Connecticut State College (ca 1978), May A. Green's Danbury Teachers College; A Brief History (ca 1950); and, Jack V. Friel's research notes, which contain alphabetical and numerical lists of his oral history interviews, background history of the school, and a proposed outline of his research paper. Friel's annotated summaries of his interviews are filed within the appropriate presidential term. His oral history tapes are located in the Jack V. Friel University History Collection in the Ruth A. Haas Library, Archives & Special Collections Department.
File folders that contain an individual's name in parenthesis identify the source of the information within the folder. Faculty folders under Haas, Bersi, and Feldman contain obituaries and summaries of interviews with the following members of the faculty: Helen (McGlynn) Cuming (class of 1926), Elizabeth McNamara (class of 1928), Ralph Brabanti (class of 1941), Rabbi Jerome Malino; Mary Brennan Musnicki and Elsie Laurincella Rader (class of 1939); Mort Johnson (class of 1942); Trudy Braun; and, Helen Tucker (class of 1929); Jack Friel (2000); Truman A. Warner, and Gertrude M. Murphy (Friel interview 1976).
The first president of Danbury Normal School was John R. Perkins (1903-1923). The personal files contain biographical information, research notes, clippings, and news coverage of Perkins' death. Folder 17 contains correspondence with John C. Perkins (grandson of JRP), Town History Papers of the Monday Club of Washington, Conn. Reminiscences of Dr. Orlando Brown Written by His Wife Martha Pomeroy Whittlesey In the Eighty-Third Year of Her Age and The "New" Danbury Normal School circa 1903 by Margaret Perkins (Mrs. Mortimer H. Camp), daughter of John R. Perkins.
Of special interest are profiles of students who entered DNS between 1904 and 1906, excerpts from admission forms (1907-1912), and copies of letters of inquiry from prospective students (box 1, folder 24). Also included are reminiscences by Janine K. (Brentari) Brennan (class of 1984), and A Tree Grows in Danbury; and, Memories and Vagaries, Wanderings and Meanderings, Kindergarten, 1916-1917, in the Old Main by Dr. William P. Georgen (class of 1917).
The second president of DNS was Lothrop Higgins (1923-1935). The personal file contains several obituaries, a questionnaire from Brown University, his alma mater, and annotated summaries of two interviews by Jack Friel with Minnie Benham (Mrs. Llewellyn Warner) DNS graduate 1911, and Jennie Warner (Mrs. Frank Stone) DNS graduate 1917 and cousin to Truman Warner.
The Student Life files (box 1, folders 34-35) contain research notes, obituaries, reunions, and minutes of meetings of the Student Cooperative Government Association between 1926 and 1930. Summaries of interviews by HFJ include Mary Creagh (class of 1927), Ann Girlometti (class of 1928), Helen Budd Mason (class of 1923), Helen McGlynn Cuming (class of 1926), and a transcript of Gertrude Murphy's (class of 1912) reminisces of DNS.
Two booklets prepared for the Golden Circle Luncheons of October 16, 1998, and October 8, 1999, contain alphabetical lists of alumnae and their personal and career highlights since graduation. Mary Creagh donated two photographs of students on a field trip (site unknown, ca. 1926-1927) which are located in box one, folder 34.
Ralph C. Jenkins was the school's third president (1935 to 1946). The personal files contain biographical information, clippings, his opening remarks at the beginning of the college year, September 7, 1943, and a portion of his manuscript Henry Barnard-Progressive Educator of Teachers. A reprint of his manuscript from The Educational Forum, November 1939, is also included. See also Ralph C. Jenkins Collection.
Interviews by HFJ include Mary Breennan Musnicki, Elizabeth Laws, Elsie Lauricella Rader, Charlotte Isham, and also Jack Friel's interview with Charlotte Isham in 1976.
Elizabeth (Libby) Laws (nee Minck) was a student at DTC (class of 1942). Folder 51 contains her Plan Book, Mrs. Dobson, Miry Brook clippings, and copies of photographs from yearbooks that includes Miry Brook, Mill Plain, Locust Avenue, and Balmforth Avenue Schools. Libby Laws also donated 42 photographs to the archives that depict student life (ca 1938-1942) The images are also filed in folder 51.
Ruth A. Haas was the school's fourth president (1946-1975). The personal files contain newspaper clippings, copies of correspondence, Tribute to a Great Lady by Jim Dyer, and summaries of HFJ's interviews with Joseph Batchelor (brother-in-law to RAH), Doris Salmon (class of 1932); and, Jack Friel's interviews with Ruth A. Haas and Corinne D. O'Connell (1976). See also Ruth A. Haas Collection.
The Interim Program was designed for freshmen and sophomore students to participate in and successfully complete an actual work experience project during one month between semesters in a non-paying position with business, government agency, or non-profit organizations. Summary reports, committee recommendations, and opinion surveys are located in box 2, folders 15-16. See also An Evaluation of a Field Experience Program; The Danbury State Teachers College Interim Program. A Report of a Type C Project by Calvin C. Eland, (box 2, folder 8).
The Monuments of Culture program (box 2, folders 17-18) was a short lived attempt to integrate music, art, science, and humanities courses into a four year, interdisciplinary course sequence that would fulfill the general education requirement for elementary education teachers. The files contain syllabuses for 1958-1959, and an interview with Martha Counts, who designed and taught this program along with Lou Edwards, Jim Timmins, and Fred Lowe during 1958-1959.
The Nature of Man Program (box 2, folder 19) was an interdisciplinary program in Humanistic Studies. This file contains a transcript of an interview with Dr. H. Jonathan Greenwald, founder of the program, by Jack Friel in 1976. For further information regarding these programs, see Record Group 8, Academic Programs.
Student Activism (box 2, folders 33-34) contains A Mild Shout: Anti-War Protest at Western Connecticut State College, 1967-1969 by Colleen Blair, and An Assessment of the Community Needs of Danbury, Connecticut, and Potential Role of Danbury State College In Community Service by David Wilder.
During Haas's tenure, DSC faculty developed three innovative teaching programs: The Interim Program, Monuments of Culture, and the Nature of Man (box 2, folders 15-19). Additional information can be found in Record Group 8, Academic Programs.
The Students files contain Jack Friel's interview with Sheila Shearon (class of 1949), and, Herb HFJ's interviews with Jack Sikora (class of 1965); Harriet Rosenberg (class of 1961); Ben DaSilva (class of 1954); Joe Lehney (class of 1953); Edyce (Dashiff) Hornig (class of 1948); and Harriet Blum (class of 1953).
Robert M. Bersi was the school's fifth president (1975-1981). The Faculty files include interviews with Dr. Ruth Kohl, Mrs. Pfender, Dr. M. Kathleen McGrory, Leslie L. LaFond, Harold R. Burke, Dr. Donald Groff, Dr. Mervin W. Whitcomb, William G. McKee, Dr. Alice I. Donnelly, Dr. F. Burton Cook, Chester E. Floyd, Dr. William J. Esposito, Neil E. Wagner, Ed Rosenberg and Clair and Al Geddes. A biography of James Furman by Howard Tuvelle and newspaper clippings focusing on Furman's musical career are also included. A summary of HFJ's interviews with Bill Devlin (class of 1976), Ray Lubus (class of 1980), and Joyce Luongo Flanagan (class of 1978) are located in Students (box 1, folder 58).
Origins of the Westside Campus can be found in box 2, folders 62-66. Information includes a thesis entitled Land Use History of the Westside Nature Preserve, Senior Research by Margaret Jackson, May 17, 2000; Expansion Proposal for Western Connecticut State College, 1968-1975; and Why Build It Now, WCSC (ca 1975). Also included are notes from a taped interview with John Deegan (1976), correspondence and interview with Arnold Hansen, Office of Institutional Planning, and architect John M. Johansen. See also box 2, folder 48, Board of Trustees (1965-1980).
Stephen Feldman was the sixth president of the school (1982-1992). Information regarding his tenure and leadership of the school, and controversies surrounding it, are contained in clippings, correspondence, and faculty interviews with Ray Baubles, Paul Hines, Howard Russock, Harry Schramm, Phil Steinkrauss, Jim Wohlever, Vijay Nair, Connie Wilds, Jack Leopold, J. Bannister, N. Jahlbert, Trudy Braun, Jim Pegolotti, Jean Main, and Neil Wagner. Copies of the underground newspapers WasteCann, Jim Crow Times, The White Street Journal, focused on faculty and student unrest during this time period. Researchers should also see the Truman Warner Collection and the University Archives for additional information.
James R. Roach is the Seventh President (1992-2004). The personal files contain clippings, an interview by JFH, and several reports related to enrollment and student characteristics, race and affirmative action issues, marketing plans, surveys, and accreditation. The clippings focus mainly on sports, faculty, administration, donors, and new construction on the campus.
Series 2, Center for Urban Studies was organized in 1981 with a coalition of Western Connecticut State University faculty from many disciplines and civic leaders from the ten town greater Danbury region. The organization was to foster greater cooperation between the college and the community, particularly in dealing with problems related to regional growth. The Center also allowed faculty to contribute to the community by offering their expertise in connection with the program.
Project Acorn: The Greening of WestConn was conceived by the all-volunteer Center for Urban Studies and supported by the college administration, Alumni Association, and the midtown dorm council. The project called for planting shade trees, evergreens, flowering trees and flower, and installing brick patios, flagstone paths, outside seating arrangements, additional stairs, pathways and ramps around the Ruth A. Haas Library.
Series 3, Subject Files, contains correspondence during Janick's tenure as Chairman of the History Department. These files contain information relating to faculty and department meetings, curriculum issues, course outlines, and student concerns.
Clio, a student publication, was designed to include articles on all areas and aspects of history. Students, including alumnae and faculty, were encouraged to contribute to the magazine. HFJ was advisor to Clio from its inception in 1973 until 1998. A complete set of Clio is filed separately under Student Publications.
As part of HFJ's Introduction to Historical Research class, students were assigned oral history projects that resulted in the following: 15 interviews with residents of Danbury who experienced the flood of 1955; 65 interviews with WCSU faculty and staff regarding the school's history; one WW II interview; and, one focused on the hatting industry in Danbury. These tapes provide a rich resource of primary source material for researchers on the topics listed above. The audiotapes and indexes are filed separately. Researchers should also see HFJ's Danbury Hatters Collection concerning the labor dispute between Dietrich Loewe and Martin Lawlor.
For additional information, researchers are encouraged to read Herbert F. Janick's book A People's University; The Centennial History of Western Connecticut State University, 1903-2003, which is available in the circulating collection of the Ruth A. Haas Library.
Arrangement
Organized in chronological and alphabetical order.
The files are grouped into 3 series:
Missing Title
Centennial Manuscript, 1889-2002
Center for Urban Studies, 1971-1988 (w/gaps)
Subject Files, 1862-2002 (w/gaps
Related Material
Geddes Collection.
Jack V. Friel University History Collection.
James Furman Collection.
June Goodman Collection.
Ruth A. Haas Papers.
Ralph C. Jenkins Papers.
Truman A. Warner Collection.
Connecticut -- Schools.; Connecticut -- Genealogy.; Ohio -- Genealogy.; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Connecticut.; Hat trade -- Connecticut -- Danbury .; Education, Higher -- Connecticut .; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Prisoners and prisons.; Steamboat disasters -- Mississippi River -- History -- 19th century; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Regimental histories -- Connecticut; College Teaching -- Connecticut.; Labor unions -- United States -- History; Clippings.; Scrapbooks.; Audiotapes.; Publications.; Correspondence.; Manuscripts (for publication).; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Personal narratives.; Ohio -- United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865; Education -- Connecticut -- History .; Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Danbury (Conn.); Oral histories (document genres).; Theses.; Feldman, Stephen.; Danbury State College.; Friel, John V.; Danbury Normal School.; Braun, Gertrude (Trudy); Blair, Colleen; Furman, James, 1937-1989; Dyer, James E.; Davis, Jerrold H.; Allen, Dorothy C.; Danbury State Teachers College.; Eckberg, Arvid Walker, 1867-1; Bersi, Robert M.; Averill, Donald C.; Jenkins, Ralph Carlton, 1891-; Janick, Herbert F.; Wilder, David E.; Pratte, Richard Norman; Pernal, Michael Edward; The Forum Club.; Sultana (Steamboat).; Warner, Gertrude Chandler; Sheridan, Vincent, Capt.; Walker, Donald E.; Western Connecticut State College.; WasteCann.; Greenwald, H. Jonathan; Leopold, Jack; Muska, Frank J.; Obeda, Barbara A.; Eland, Calvin C.; Ely, John C.; Eyre, Laurence, 1881-1959; Farnham, Thomas; Frost, Arthur Charles, Jr.; Western Connecticut State University; Frost, James Arthur
- Series 1: Centennial - Manuscript, 39118
  Scope and Contents note
  Correspondence, course catalogs, instructional programs, publications, reports, accreditation, clippings, photographs, and interviews of faculty, administrators, students and friends; and, student organizations, theses, publications, clippings, and scrapbooks
  - Correspondence, 49837
    - Correspondence, 1986, 2001-2003; 39226 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Histories, 39219
    - Farnham, Thomas, 1993; 39225 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Friel, Jack V., 1976-1977; 39224 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    - Greene, May E., 1950; 39223 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Isham, Charlotte H., 1978; 39222 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Janick, Herbert F., 2002; 39221 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Warner, Truman A., 1994-1995; 39220 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Perkins Years, 1903-1923, 39211
    - Conditions in the Schools, 1899-1903; 39218 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Danbury News, 1902-1909; 39217 (Box 1, Folder 12-15)
    - Danbury News, 1923; 39216 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Perkins - Personal, 1915-1999; 39215 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
    - Report of the State Board of Education, 1904-1924; 39214 (Box 1, Folder 19-21)
    - State Education Department to 1920s, 39213 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
    - Student Life, 1904-1923; 39212 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Higgins Years, 1924-1935, 39203
    - Danbury News-Times, 1924-1927; 39210 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - DeeNesS, 1931-1935; 39209 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1920s; 39208 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Higgins - Personal, 1925-1999; 39207 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Reports of the State Education Department, 1921-1935; 39206 (Box 1, Folder 29-32)
    - State Normal School, Reorganization, (Farnham Notes), 1920s-1930s; 39205 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Student Life, 1903-1999; 39204 (Box 1, Folder 34-35)
      General
      Mary Creagh donated two photographs (unlabeled, 3.5 x 6 b/w) of a class field trip (site unknown) dated 1926-1927.
  - Jenkins Years, 1935-1946, 39188
    - Averill, Donald C., Thesis: Responsibility of the Connecticut State Board of Education for the Education of Teachers in the State From 1865 to 1965, 1966; 39202 (Box 1, Folder 36-38)
    - Campus Newspapers, 1938-1947; 39201 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Catalogs, 1936-1941; 39200 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Danbury News-Times, 1935-1937; 39199 (Box 1, Folder 41-42)
    - Forst, Arthur Charles, Jr. Thesis: From Normal School to State College: The Growth and Development of Eastern Connecticut State College from 1889 to 1959, 1980; 39198 (Box 1, Folder 43-45)
    - Forum, 1928-1945; 39197 (Box 1, Folder 46-47)
    - Jenkins - Personal, 1919-1999; 39196 (Box 1, Folder 48-50)
    - Laws, Elizabeth (Libby), 1938-1942; 39195 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Pernal, Michael E., A Study of State Legislation in the Development of Public Higher Education in Connecticut From 1849-1976, 1975; 39194 (Box 1, Folder 52-55)
    - Pratte, Richard Norman, A History of Teacher Education in Connecticut, from 1639 to 1939., 1967; 39193 (Box 1, Folder 56-60)
    - Scrapbooks, 1934-1944; 39192 (Box 1, Folder 61-68)
    - State Department of Education, 1929-1939; 39191 (Box 1, Folder 69-72)
    - Student Cooperative Government Association, 1930-1938; 39190 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Student Life, 1930-2000; 39189 (Box 1, Folder 74-75)
  - Haas Years, 1946-1976, 39166
    - Accreditation, 1953; 39187 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Boston Trip, 1953; 39186 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Campus Newspapers, 1948-1957; 39185 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Catalogs, 1960-1970; 39184 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Danbury News-Times (Truman), 1960-1969; 39183 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Echo (copies), 1960-1973; 39182 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
    - Eland, Calvin C. Dissertation: An Evaluation of a Field Experience Program; The Danbury State Teachers College Interim Program. A Report of a Type C Project., 1957; 39181 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Faculty, 1928-2000; 39180 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
    - Haas - Personal, 1922-1999; 39179 (Box 2, Folder 11-14)
    - Interim Program, 1947-1956; 39178 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
    - Monuments of Culture Program, 1958-1960; 39177 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
    - Nature of Man Program, 1967-2000; 39176 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Reaccredidation, 1963; 39175 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Scrapbooks, 1945-1964; 39174 (Box 2, Folder 21-27)
    - State Department of Education, 1946-1960; 39173 (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
    - State Reorganization-1965, 1949-1992; 39172 (Box 2, Folder 30-31)
    - Stratemeyer/Columbia, 1924-2000; 39171 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Student Activism, 1967-1970; 39170 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
    - Students, 1975-2000; 39169 (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
    - Teacher's Do's, 1950-1955; 39168 (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
    - Truman, 1970-1975; 39167 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bersi Years, 1974-1982, 39152
    - Accreditation, 1973; 39165 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Arts Festival/Ives Center, 1974-2000; 39164 (Box 2, Folder 41-42)
    - Basic Studies, 1982-2000; 39163 (Box 2, Folder 43-45)
    - Bersi--Personal, 1975-2000; 39162 (Box 2, Folder 46-47)
    - Board of Trustees, 1965-1980; 39161 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Clippings (Truman Files), 1970-1981; 39160 (Box 2, Folder 49-51)
    - Echo (copies), 1971-1981; 39159 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Economics, Politics, 1960-1970s; 39158 (Box 2, Folder 53-54)
    - Faculty, 1976-2000; 39157 (Box 2, Folder 55-57)
    - Students, 1970-1981; 39156 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Truman, 1975-1981; 39155 (Box 2, Folder 59-60)
    - Union, 1972-2000; 39154 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Westside Campus, 1964-2000; 39153 (Box 2, Folder 62-66)
  - Feldman Years, 1982-1992, 39130
    - AAUP, 1987-1989; 39151 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - Accreditation, 1983; 39150 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Articles and Misc. (Steinkrauss), 1987-1993; 39149 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
    - Athletics, 1959-2001; 39148 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Basic Studies, 1980s; 39147 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Board of Trustees, 1982-1991; 39146 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
    - Braun, Trudy, 1948-2001; 39145 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Interviews, 2000-2001; 39144 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1983-1990; 39143 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Clippings (summaries), 1983-1991; 39142 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Echo (copies), 1982-1992; 39141 (Box 3, Folder 15-17)
    - Feldman (Leopold/Danbury News-Times), 1987-1989; 39140 (Box 3, Folder 18-20)
    - Feldman (Leopold), 1988; 39139 (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
    - Feldman/Muska Evaluation (Leopold), 1988-1989; 39138 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Feldman - Personal, 1982-2001; 39137 (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
    - Paper for T. C., 1987; 39136 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Public Relations, 1991-2001; 39135 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Underground Publications, 1987-1989, 2000; 39134 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - University Foundation, 1979-1988; 39133 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - WasteCann (Leopold), 1987; 39132 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - WCSU Senior Faculty Concerns, Inactive (Krizinger), 1987-1988; 39131 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - James R. Roach, 1992-2004, 39119
    - Accreditation, 1992-1998; 39129 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Echo (summaries), 1992-1996; 39128 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Rosters, 1967-1997; 39127 (Box 3, Folder 34-36)
    - History of WCSU, 1937; 39126 (Box 3, Folder 37-39)
    - Muska, 1976-1984; 39125 (Box 3, Folder 40-42)
    - Newspapers/Public Affairs, 1997-2000; 39124 (Box 3, Folder 43-45)
    - Race/Affirmative Action, 1990-1994; 39123 (Box 3, Folder 46-48)
    - Roach - Personal, 1992-1996; 39122 (Box 3, Folder 49-51)
    - Truman - History Talk/Commencement, 1995; 39121 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Wilcox, Jerry - Institutional Research & Assessment, 1980-2002; 39120 (Box 3, Folder 53-54)
- Series 2: The Center for Urban Studies, 39098
  Correspondence, reports, internship applications, programs, clippings, pamphlets, oral history, and flyers.
  - Annual Reports, 1982-1983; 39117 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Bear Mountain-Natural and Scenic, 1971-1982; 39116 (Box 3, Folder 56-58)
  - Campus as a Community Resource, 1978-1982; 39115 (Box 3, Folder 59-61)